310-962-0030 jb@motionmusic.us 3059 Dona Susana Dr. Studio City, CA 91604

Profile

Passionate and Innovative Live Music & Event Director and Producer with over 16 years of experience producing and executing Live Shows, Music Tours and Events, and TV Appearances in over 90 countries for millions of fans. Known for creating truly immersive and engaging events and shows, while still being able to accurately project all financials and manage large teams of performers, crews, and vendors. Created a proprietary system for tracking expenses in real time to enable the customer to make changes to their Music Tour and Events before it's too late. This includes utilizing this system to recognize trends in sales & expenses, and adjusting course when needed. Able to recognize talent and potential in staff, and build specialized teams to accomplish complex goals while minimizing costs. Personally invests in team members to maximize their potential.

Experience

PRESIDENT, MOTION MUSIC; LOS ANGELES, CA - 2008-PRESENT

Founded and currently running Motion Music. Motion Music produces Tours, Live Events, and TV Appearances globally. It also serves as a Live Entertainment Business Resource for Artists, Managers, Labels, Business Managers, Agents, and Brands. Services include Events & Touring, Festivals, Creative Services, Merchandising, Rentals, and VIP M&G Programs. Motion Music has been able to carry out massive multi-million dollars shows and tours in over 90 countries around the World in front of over 500,000,000 fans in the past decade. It has taken part in some of the biggest shows Globally to date including The 2012 London Olympics Closing Ceremony, 2012 EUFA Euro Cup Finals, Formula 1 Races in Monaco, Bahrain, Singapore, many yearly finales of Television Shows like American Idol, The Voice, X-Factor, Dancing with the Stars, and massive Festival, Arena, and Stadium performances and Tours. Artist roster over the years include Frank Ocean, Bruno Mars, Tears for Fears, A\$AP Rocky, ODESZA, Julia Michaels, Guns & Roses, Ariana Grande, Deftones, Miguel, Maxwell, Louis The Child, Moby, Il Volo, Elle King, Christina Perri, Grimes, Taio Cruz and many more.

TOUR, PRODUCTION & CREATIVE DIRECTOR, JULIA MICHAELS; GLOBAL - 2017-PRESENT

Worked along side Julia Michael's management to transform Julia from one of the most prolific & powerful songwriters in the last decade to a full on Pop Star Phenomenon. This includes creating and producing her entire live show by designing, staffing, budgeting, and negotiating deals & endorsements with vendors globally resulting in over a million dollars worth of free equipment and marketing investment. Managed millions of dollars of show deals and created budgets that made the client substantial profits, while minimizing costs. Tours included Shawn Mendes in Australia, Pink & Maroon 5 in the US, Niall Horan in Europe, and Keith Urban in Australia. Produced & Creative Directed her first ever Global Headlining Tour based on a specific album cycle and cohesive branding. Took part in

Creating & Producing all TV performances, including The Grammys, The Billboard Awards, The MTV EMA Awards, The Today Show, Jimmy Kimmel Live, The Tonight Show wt Jimmy Fallon, and many others around the World. Created an entire Merch Line which netted hundreds of thousands of dollars both on tour and as part of an custom online store (up to \$15/head in some markets), and created various immersive VIP M&G Experiences that added six figures of additional income to the tours. Shows: 250+ in front of over 2 million fans in 29 countries. Instagram followers up from 200k to over 2 million.

PRODUCTION & TECHNICAL DIRECTOR, ODESZA; GLOBAL - 2017-PRESENT

Hired at the beginning of the multiple Grammy Award Nominated Album "A Moment Apart" album cycle to begin scaling up Production and Creative Concepts in order to play Arena size venues like the Staple Center Arena in Los Angeles and Barclays Center Arena in Brooklyn. Creative Consulting and Production Direction, including staffing & budgeting, Technical Director for the larger shows. Responsible for negotiating a deal between Odesza and French audio speaker manufacturer L'Acoustic to launch the first ever L'Acoustic L'ISA Show which enables artists to create & deliver new multidimensional sound experiences for live concert. Other Show highlights include the performance at Coachella 2018, where the promoter Goldenvoice said we created many firsts that year, including the first to ever use lighting drones in an outdoors live concert, and the first to ever use the full 10k screen as one single screen during a 34 second moment (which took almost a full day to render). Shows: 146 in front of over 2.8 million fans in 25 countries.

TOUR, PRODUCTION & CREATIVE DIRECTOR, TEAR FOR FEARS; GLOBAL – 2010-PRESENT TOUR, PRODUCTION & CREATIVE DIRECTOR, TAIO CRUZ; GLOBAL – 2010-PRESENT TOUR, PRODUCTION DIRECTOR, JAI WOLF; GLOBAL – 2019-PRESENT TOUR, PRODUCTION DIRECTOR, LOUIS THE CHILD; GLOBAL – 2019-PRESENT TOUR, PRODUCTION DIRECTOR, MAXWELL; GLOBAL – 2019-PRESENT PRODUCTION DIRECTOR, FLUME; GLOBAL – 2020-PRESENT PAST CLIENTS AND EXPERIENCE AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST

Education

University of Miami, Florida – Bachelor of Arts in Music, Music Business & Entertainment Industries Minor, Psychology Minor, 2006

Skills

Global Touring Experience and Show Production in over 90 countries

Full knowledge of all things LIVE / Production, including Audio, Lighting, Video, Backline, Lasers, Special FX, Staging, Rigging, Automation

Cultivating Relationships including Music Labels, Television & Radio Stations, and Vendors around the World

Languages: English, French, Spanish, and some German

Management of Touring & Production teams of up to 150+ people

Marketing including creating plans for the launch of Tours and Live Music Events via advertising (print, radio, and online) and timing on-sale schedules

Social Media Management and Strategies including Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Snapchat, Tik Tok

Merchandising, including soft good and fashion trends, design, accounting (including venue splits, commissions, and taxes), and implementation of new technologies like AtVenu

Computer: Mac/PC, iOS, MS Office, Apple Work Suite, Adobe Creative Suite, Avid ProTools and other DAWs, MasterTour, Vectorworks (CAD)

Currently learning computer coding including UX, front end and back end OS and iOS development (Xcode, Swift, Objective C) via UCLA Coding Bootcamp

References

Chris Knight, RocNation - General Manager of Artist Management - knight@rocnation.com

Beka Tischker, Wide Eyed Entertainment - President - beka@wideeyedent.com

Kevin Kanegai, NKSFBGO - Partner - kkanegai@nksfb.com

Brian Manning, CAA - Agent - bmanning@caa.com

Gary Gersh, AEG Presents - President, Global Touring & Talent - <u>ggersh@aegpresents.com</u> *More references available upon request.*